{
    "subject": "resource/Anne_Sjerp_Troelstra",
    "predicate": "ontology/doctoralAdvisor",
    "object": "resource/Arend_Heyting",
    "human_readable": "Anne Sjerp Troelstra was advised by Arend Heyting during her doctoral studies.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9866148829460144,
            "question": "Who advised Anne Sjerp Troelstra during her doctoral studies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9740896821022034,
            "question": "Was Arend Heyting involved in Anne Sjerp Troelstra's education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8923131227493286,
            "question": "What role did Arend Heyting play in Anne Sjerp Troelstra's academic journey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8422315716743469,
            "question": "What was the relationship between Arend Heyting and Anne Sjerp Troelstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8372692465782166,
            "question": "What field of study might Anne Sjerp Troelstra be involved in based on her advisor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8339762687683105,
            "question": "What kind of studies was Anne Sjerp Troelstra pursuing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8003482818603516,
            "question": "Who is Anne Sjerp Troelstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7791501879692078,
            "question": "Did Arend Heyting mentor any other students besides Anne Sjerp Troelstra?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5952736139297485,
            "question": "Who is Arend Heyting?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5553101897239685,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Arend Heyting's contributions to academia?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Anne Sjerp Troelstra was advised by Arend Heyting during her doctoral studies.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7589_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Arend Heyting?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7589_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Arend Heyting mentor any other students besides Anne Sjerp Troelstra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7589_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Anne Sjerp Troelstra?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7589_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7589_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as it is stated that \"His interests converged on intuitionism with Arend Heyting as his advisor.\" and also mentioned that Anne Troelstra's PhD thesis was supervised by Heyting."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that Anne Sjerp Troelstra was supervised by Arend Heyting for his dissertation on Intuitionistic General Topology, which confirms the statement."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}